We have three jobs to run sequentially.
The first one is right here
and then followed by the rod curated
and then the curated to aggregated script.
Okay, so we'll ask Amazon Q to get us something called
as a SL code is.
It still stands for Amazon States Language Code.
That is the code using which we build step functions.
You'll see it shortly. In fact,
I say give gimme an A SL code
for a step function named this.
The first one will be data on router followed by the raw
to curated and then they curated to the raw jobs.
Okay? Make sure to also send an alert
to SNS topic called mission, D-E-H-H-O-F,
if there's any failure at all in any of the glue jobs.
Okay? Now the second job should not run
until the first one is finished.
It is important, okay? And the third one should not run
until the second one is finished.
Okay? Now this is what I mean by sudo code before, okay?
You're able to communicate your thoughts with Amazon Q.
Now you're asking Amazon Q to give me a step function,
SL code, yes, but the step function is something
that can really call the glue job.
But here all we have are the scripts Step function,
doesn't know the glue job names, okay?
These are the simple scripts.
So we could, could also provide amazing q
the glue job names.
So I go to glue, get my job names
and I have put them right here in the brackets.
You should also ask, do you need anything else from
me at this point
before you can get me the a SL code?
There you go. It has, it has everything.
It needs to create step function, a SL code.
And we have the entire uh, JSON file ready here.
In fact, this is the a SL code.
In fact, this you'll see shortly, in fact again,
when we'll use this to create the step function.
Okay? So it has done a better job in fact, okay?
It is saying different failure messages for each job stage.
I hadn't even thought about this.
And it's saying to deploy the step function unit, need
to create the mission dhh.
We already done that. We have
already have the SNS topic here.
It needs the permission. Yes, we have got the permissions
by asking to our cloud engineer team
and they've already, uh, added the permissions to us,
which we'll use in the next step.
And we gotta replace the region and the account.
So we know that we should be using US East one in the
bo in the program, in fact.
So let's just tell amazing Q that the region needs to be
US East one.
And as you see here, it has updated the region as well.
Okay? We just have to update our account id.
So let's do that next video.